

# Pejman Kiamehr

# Junior React front-end Developer

## Summary

Experienced React Developer More than 1 year of experience in website development and also organizational panels with **React**. Familiarity with **Restfull Api** and experience of cooperation with **Backend Developer**, proficient in **Responsive Design** and familiarity with **SEO**. I am currently looking for an opportunity to work with a team of several front-end developers.

## Contact Information

Phone 0915 550 3369

Email pejman.kiamehr@gmail.com

## Work samples

MyWebsite www.pejmankiamehr.ir

Github https://github.com/pejmankiamehr

## Technical Skills

 $React Js \quad context API, restfull Api, react Bootstrap, Material UI, Ant Desing, Responsive Design, react Hooks, axios the property of the pr$ 

 $fundamentals \quad HTML, CSS, JavaScript, E6, Media-Query, Bootstrap, JQuery, Less$ 

VC Git, Github, Gitlab

Others postman, figma, trello, Scrum, Latex

# Professional Experiences

2023–2024 **Customer affairs expert**, mashhad.

Iran server (Green Web)

2021–2022 React front-end Developer, Mashhad.

Eight Team

2018–2020 **Customer affairs expert**, *Tehran*.

Romak Holding (Snapp Team)

2016–2017 Website admin. Mashhad.

Yekta Mana Company

2015–2016 Content production specialist, Mashhad.

Yekta Mana Company

### Education

2019–2020 **Tehran Institute of Technology**, *Tehran*.

Web Package Design: web1,web2,web3

2009-2013 Islamic Azad University, Mashhad.

BSc. of Mechanical Engineering

### Soft skills

- 1. Embraces teamwork, Team-oriented personality
- 2. Excellent written and verbal communication skills
- 3. Excellent presentation and negotiation skills